Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive, 1960-2004 (Bulk 1973-2000) MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Video, 155690
  - Subseries B: Originals - Video, 155710
    - Second Hand Hitler (First Version, Part 2), ID 221.0076; 155782 (Box 75, Media ID 221.0076)
    - Second Hand Hitler (First Version), August 1985; ID 221.0077; 155783 (Box 75, Media ID 221.0077)
    - Violent Femmes (Subtitled Version), ID 221.0078; 155784 (Box 75, Media ID 221.0078)
      TRT: [28 minutes]
    - Lotringer video on writer Pierre Guyotat, Oct 19, 1984, 10/19/84; ID 221.0079; 155785 (Box 75, Media ID 221.0079)
    - Lotringer video on writer Pierre Guyotat, Oct 18, 1984, 10/18/84; ID 221.0080; 155786 (Box 75, Media ID 221.0080)
    - "Lightning Over Water" (First Version), ID 221.0081; 155787 (Box 75, Media ID 221.0081)
    - "Lightning Over Water" (Second Version), ID 221.0082; 155788 (Box 75, Media ID 221.0082)
    - Films on Felix Guattari - Tape 1, ID 221.0083; 155789 (Box 75, Media ID 221.0083)
    - Films on Felix Guattari - Tape 2, ID 221.0084; 155790 (Box 75, Media ID 221.0084)
    - Films on Felix Guattari - Tape 3, ID 221.0085; 155791 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0085)
    - Entretiens avec Felix Guattari [Interviews with Felix Guattari], ID 221.0086; 155792 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0086)
    - Museum of Accidents (Paul Virilio et. al.), ID 221.0087; 155793 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0087)
    - Video with Julia Kristeva, ID 221.0088; 155794 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0088)
    - Baudrillard Interview, ID 221.0089; 155795 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0089)
    - Body and Technology Talk by Sylvere Lotringer, ID 221.0090; 155796 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0090)
    - Sylvere Lotringer interviewed by Austrian artist Rainer Ganahil on Biography (in French), ID 221.0091; 155797 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0091)
    - "Simone Weil and Judaism" - Tape 1, 11/14/96; ID 221.0092; 155798 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0092)
      Note: No accompanying tapes have been found.
    - "The Set-Up" (Kathryn Bigelow), ID 221.0093; 155799 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0093)
    - "get rid of yourself", ID 221.0094; 155800 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0094)
    - Marion Scemama on Dave Wojnarowicz + interview by Sylvere, ID 221.0095; 155801 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0095)
    - Late Show, Henri Matisse (includes an interview with Sylvere), ID 221.0096; 155802 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0096)
    - Footage for Second Hand Hitler - Tape 1 (NTSC Transfer), ID 221.0097; 155816 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0097)
    - Footage for Second Hand Hitler - Tape 2 (NTSC Transfer), ID 221.0098; 155817 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0098)
    - Footage for Second Hand Hitler - Tape 3 (NTSC Transfer), ID 221.0099; 155818 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0099)
    - Footage for Second Hand Hitler - Tape 3B (NTSC Transfer), ID 221.0100; 155819 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0100)
    - Footage for Second Hand Hitler - Tape 4 (NTSC Transfer), ID 221.0101; 155820 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0101)
    - Footage for Second Hand Hitler - Tape 4B (NTSC Transfer), ID 221.0102; 155821 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0102)
    - Footage for Second Hand Hitler - Tape 5 (NTSC Transfer), ID 221.0103; 155822 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0103)
    - Footage for Second Hand Hitler - Tape 6 (NTSC Transfer), ID 221.0104; 155823 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0104)
    - Footage for Second Hand Hitler - Tape 7 (NTSC Transfer), ID 221.0105; 155824 (Box 76, Media ID 221.0105)
    - Violentes Femmes, ID 221.0106; 155825 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0106)
    - Violentes Femmes (Subtitled Version), ID 221.0107; 155826 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0107)
    - Violentes Femmes (Subtitled Version), ID 221.0108; 155827 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0108)
    - Violent Femmes (No Subtitles), Victoire & Catherine Robbe-Grillet, ID 221.0109; 155828 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0109)
    - Violentes Femmes (Edit Master), ID 221.0110; 155829 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0110)
    - Violentes Femmes (Subtitled, Edit Master), ID 221.0111; 155830 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0111)
    - Interview footage for How to Shoot a Crime and Violent Femmes - Tape 7, ID 221.0112; 155831 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0112)
    - Interview footage for How to Shoot a Crime and Violent Femmes - Tape 8, ID 221.0113; 155832 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0113)
    - Interview footage for How to Shoot a Crime and Violent Femmes - Tape 9, ID 221.0114; 155833 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0114)
    - Interview footage for How to Shoot a Crime and Violent Femmes - Tape 10, ID 221.0115; 155834 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0115)
    - Interview footage for How to Shoot a Crime and Violent Femmes - Tape 11, ID 221.0116; 155835 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0116)
    - Serology/ Crime Scene - Tape 1, ID 221.0117; 155836 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0117)
    - Crime Scene - #3, ID 221.0118; 155837 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0118)
    - Crime Scene - #4, ID 221.0119; 155838 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0119)
    - Oprah Winfrey Show - 9/23/86 WABC - 10am-11am "Rape Victims" Part I, ID 221.0120; 155839 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0120)
    - Unknown tape 1, originally stored in box labeled Hitler/ Violent Femmes, ID 221.0121; 155840 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0121)
    - Unknown tape 2, originally stored in box labeled Hitler/ Violent Femmes, ID 221.0122; 155841 (Box 77, Media ID 221.0122)
    - Unknown tape 3, originally stored in box labeled Hitler/ Violent Femmes, ID 221.0123; 155842 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0123)
    - How to Shoot a Crime, ID 221.0124; 155843 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0124)
    - Chris Kraus short films: Foolproof Illusion, Voyage of Rodez, Terrorist in Love, How to Shoot a Crime, ID 221.0125; 155844 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0125)
    - Unknown tape, originally stored in box labeled 'The Chance Event', ID 221.0126; 155845 (Box 78, Case 221.0126)
    - Films on Felix Guattari - Tape 4, ID 221.0127; 155846 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0127)
    - Films on Felix Guattari - Tape 5, ID 221.0128; 155847 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0128)
    - Films on Felix Guattari - Tape 6, ID 221.0129; 155848 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0129)
    - Geraldo Show, ID 221.0130; 155849 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0130)
      Connected with the Bin Rahad book put out by Semiotext(e): Still Black Still Strong
    - Framing the Panthers, ID 221.0131; 155850 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0131)
      Contains the Mumia Abu-Jamal interview which inspired Sylvere Lotringer to make his Black Panthers video.
    - Various films on Antonin Artaud, ID 221.0132; 155851 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0132)
    - Two programs on Antonin Artaud, ID 221.0133; 155852 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0133)
    - Antonin Artaud [2ieme], ID 221.0134; 155853 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0134)
    - Today Tonight Tomorrow (Eldon Garnet), ID 221.0135; 155854 (Box 78, Media ID 221.0135)
    - Le Chagrin et la Pitie (1iere Partie), ID 221.0136; 155855 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0136)
    - Le Chagrin et la Pitie (2ieme Partie), ID 221.0137; 155856 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0137)
    - La Musique de Terezin (Documentaire de Simon Broughton), ID 221.0138; 155857 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0138)
    - Baudrillard tape #2, ID 221.0139; 155858 (Box 79, Case 221.0139)
    - Philosophies: Y-a-t-il des criteres du beau (Video on Lyotard), ID 221.0140; 155859 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0140)
    - Jean-Francois Lyotard "Schemattitude" (realise par Sacha Goldman), ID 221.0141; 155860 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0141)
    - Philosophies: Modernite Postmodernite (Video on Lyotard), ID 221.0142; 155861 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0142)
    - Video on Simone Weil, ID 221.0143; 155862 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0143)
    - Simone Weil: Utopian Pessimist (Florence de Lussy), ID 221.0144; 155863 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0144)
    - Simone Weil (Ashoff), ID 221.0145; 155864 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0145)
    - Simone Weil, Ashoff (et les [Chr de Chamase]), ID 221.0146; 155865 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0146)
    - Films on Felix Guattari - Tape 7, ID 221.0147; 155866 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0147)
    - Archives Klein Film 1, ID 221.0148; 155867 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0148)
    - Savoir Plus (Video on Antonin Artaud), ID 221.0149; 155868 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0149)
    - "Compilation/ Extraits" (P. Huyghe), ID 221.0150; 155869 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0150)
    - Gil Wolman L'Anticoncept, ID 221.0151; 155870 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0151)
    - Border 2000 (Michal Rovner), ID 221.0152; 155871 (Box 79, Media ID 221.0152)
    - Los Pintos (Raymonde Carasco), ID 221.0153; 155881 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0153)
      One of four Raymonde Carasco tapes shown at the Antonin Artaud conference.
    - Antonin Artaud et les Tarahumaras (Raymonde Carasco), ID 221.0154; 155882 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0154)
    - Los Pascoleros (Raymonde Carasco), ID 221.0155; 155883 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0155)
      TRT: [unknown}
    - Tutuguri (Raymonde Carasco), ID 221.0156; 155926 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0156)
    - The Beat Experience (Red Hot Productions), ID 221.0157; 155927 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0157)
    - Equinox: "Theme Park Heaven", ID 221.0158; 155928 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0158)
    - Out of the Present (Andrei Ujica), ID 221.0159; 155929 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0159)
    - Unknown videotape 1, ID 221.0160; 155930 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0160)
    - Unknown videotape 2, ID 221.0161; 155931 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0161)
    - Unknown videotape 3, ID 221.0162; 155932 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0162)
    - Unknown videotape 4, ID 221.0163; 155933 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0163)
    - Boyz in New York, ID 221.0164; 155934 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0164)
      Format: Hi 8mm
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 1, ID 221.0165; 155935 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0165)
      Format: DV
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 2, ID 221.0166; 155936 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0166)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 3, ID 221.0167; 155937 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0167)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 4, ID 221.0168; 155938 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0168)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 5, ID 221.0169; 155939 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0169)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 6, ID 221.0170; 155940 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0170)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 7, ID 221.0171; 155941 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0171)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 8, ID 221.0172; 155942 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0172)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 9, ID 221.0173; 155943 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0173)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 10, ID 221.0174; 155944 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0174)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 11, ID 221.0175; 155945 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0175)
    - Simone Weil Conference - Tape 12, ID 221.0176; 155946 (Box 80, Media ID 221.0176)
    - Unknown videotape 5, ID 221.0308; 156227 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0308)
      Format: 1/2 in. open reel
    - Jim Brodey Talks…, ID 221.0309; 156228 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0309)
    - Fred Dewey/ Suzanne, ID 221.0310; 156229 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0310)
    - Ann Rower/ Suzanne, ID 221.0311; 156230 (Box 88, Media ID 221.0311)
    - Chance Event: The Chance Band, unedited footage, 1996; ID 221.0426; 189572 (Box 91, Media ID 221.0426)
    - David W., ID: 221.0454; 272051 (Box 88, Media ID: 221.0454)
      Format: 3/4" Umatic
    - David, ID: 221.0455; 272052 (Box 88, Media ID: 221.0455)
  - Subseries C: Submasters - Video - CLOSED
    Conditions Governing Access
    CLOSED
    - ID 221.0374 - 221.0393, 221.0558, 221.0560, 221.0656 (Box PM 11)
  - Subseries D: Preservation Masters - Video - CLOSED
    - ID: 221.0373 - 221.0389 (Box PM 56)
    - ID: 221.0392, 221.0456, 221.0459 (Box PM 57)
- Series XI: Audio, 155694
  - Subseries A: Access Copies - Audio, 155695
    - William Burroughs-- Excerpts from Naked Lunch (Duplicate Copy), undated; ID: 221.0463; 214659 (Case 221.0463)
      Format: CD
      TRT: 00:41:43
      Original Format: 1/4" Audio Reel
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 2, 1975; ID: 221.0465; 214660 (Case 221.0465)
      TRT: 00:32:36
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 3 (William Burroughs, Allen Ginsberg: Yage Letters, part 2 of 2), 1975; ID: 221.0467; 214661 (Case 221.0467)
      TRT: 00:34:18
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 4 (William Burroughs, The Last Words of Dutch Schultz), 1975; ID: 221.0469; 214662 (Case 221.0469)
      TRT: 00:53:02
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 5 (William Burroughs, The Last Words of Dutch Schultz), 1975; 221.0471; 214663 (Case 221.0471)
      TRT: 00:52:57
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 6 (William Burroughs, The Last Words of Dutch Schultz), 1975; ID: 221.0472; 214664 (Case 221.0472)
      TRT: 00:33:01
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 7 (William Burroughs, Allen Ginsburg: Yage Letters, part 1 of 2), 1975; ID: 221.0474; 214665 (Case 221.0474)
      TRT: 00:59:47
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 8 (William Burroughs, Naked Lunch, part 2 of 2), 1975; ID: 221.0476; 214666 (Case 221.0476)
      TRT: 00:35:12
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 9 (Intro: Lotringer/Rajchman), 1975; ID: 221.0396; 180512 (Case 221.0396)
      Format: CD-R
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 10 (Fassender), 1975; ID: 221.0398; 180513 (Case 221.0398)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 11 (Fine on Panopticon), 1975; ID: 221.0400; 180542 (Case 221.0400)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 12 (Fine cont/ responses), 1975; ID: 221.0402; 180543 (Case 221.0402)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 13 (Danto? Kovel?), 1975; ID: 221.0404; 180544 (Case 221.0404)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 14 (Danto, Lyotard), 1975; ID: 221.0406; 180545 (Case 221.0406)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 15 (Lyotard), 1975; ID: 221.0408; 180546 (Case 221.0408)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 16 (Lyotard), 1975; ID: 221.0410; 180617 (Case 221.0410)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 17 (Lyotard), ID: 221.0412; 180618 (Case 221.0412)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 18, 1975; ID: 221.0414; 180619 (Case 221.0414)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 19, 1975; ID: 221.0416; 180620 (Case 221.0416)
    - Interview with "New Novelist" Nathalie Sarraute, part 1, Late 50s; ID: 221.0418; 180621 (Case 221.0418)
    - Interview with "New Novelist" Nathalie Sarraute, part 2, Late 50s; ID: 221.0420; 180622 (Case 221.0420)
    - Interviews with members of the Bloomsbury Group, London: T.S. Eliot, Vita Sackville-West, Leonard Woolf, David Garnet, 1961; ID: 221.0422; 181113 (Case 221.0422)
      Access to cd 221.0422 is restricted.
      Format: DVD-R
    - Road Movies - "Nick's Movie" - reel 1, 1979; ID: 221.0446; 203963 (Case 221.0446)
    - Road Movies - "Nick's Movie" - reel 2, 1979; ID: 221.0447; 203964 (Case 221.0447)
    - Road Movies - "Nick's Movie" - reel 3, 1979; ID: 221.0448; 203965 (Case 221.0448)
    - Road Movies - "Nick's Movie" - reel 4, 1979; ID: 221.0449; 203966 (Case 221.0449)
    - Road Movies - "Nick's Movie" - reel 5, 1979; ID: 221.0450; 203967 (Case 221.0450)
    - Nick's Memorial - reel 1, ID: 221.0451; 203968 (Case 221.0451)
    - Nick's Memorial - reel 2, ID: 221.0452; 203969 (Case 221.0452)
    - David, ID: 221.0453; 203970 (Case 221.0453)
    - _Overexposed_ Interview with Peter Wilson, April 18, 1988 - part 2, ID: 221.0478; 214667 (Case 221.0478)
      TRT: 00:38:09
    - _Overexposed_ Interview with Peter Wilson, April 18, 1988 Side 1, Part 1, ID: 221.0480; 214668 (Case 221.0480)
    - _Overexposed_ Interview with Peter Wilson, April 18, 1988 Side 1, Part 2, ID: 221.0481; 214669 (Case 221.0481)
    - Jean-Paul Sartre lecture: "Theatre dramatique et theatre epique", Sorbonne, late 50s Side One, Part 1, ID: 221.0483; 214671 (Case 221.0483)
      TRT: 00:50:35
    - Jean-Paul Sartre lecture: "Theatre dramatique et theatre epique", Sorbonne, late 50s Side One, Part 2, ID: 221.0485; 214672 (Case 221.0485)
      TRT: 00:46:12
    - Jean-Paul Sartre lecture: "Theatre dramatique et theatre epique", Sorbonne, late 50s Side Two, ID: 221.0487; 214673 (Case 221.0487)
      TRT: 00:44:47
    - Interview with Brendan Behan, Dublin, Jan 1961 - Reel 1 Side One, Part 1, January 1961; ID: 221.0489; 214674 (Case 221.0489)
    - Interview with Brendan Behan, Dublin, Jan 1961 - Reel 1 Side One, Part 2, January 1961; ID: 221.0491; 214675 (Case 221.0491)
    - Pierre Daix in conversation with writer Michel Butor, Sorbonne, late 50s-early 60s, undated; ID: 221.0493; 214676 (Case 221.0493)
      TRT: 00:18:44
    - Interview with British filmmaker Tony Richardson, London, mid 60s (Side 1, Part 2), undated; ID: 221.0496; 214677 (Case 221.0496)
      TRT: 00:51:49
    - Interview with British filmmaker Tony Richardson, London, mid 60s (Side 1, Part 2), ID: 221.0497; 214678 (Case 221.0497)
      TRT: 01:00:06
    - Interview with British filmmaker Tony Richardson, London, mid 60s (Side 1, Part 2), ID: 221.0499; 214679 (Case 221.0499)
      TRT: 01:10:44
    - Lectures by New French Critics, Sorbonne, 1964 (presented by Lotringer)(Side One, Part 2), cuid7129; 214690 (Case 221.0501)
      TRT: 01:07:45
    - Lectures by New French Critics, Sorbonne, 1964 (presented by Lotringer)(Side One, Part 3), cuid7130; 214691 (Case 221.0503)
      TRT: 00:42:31
    - Lectures by New French Critics, Sorbonne, 1964 (presented by Lotringer)(Side Two, Part 1), cuid7131; 214692 (Case 221.0505)
      TRT: 01:04:20
    - Lectures by New French Critics, Sorbonne, 1964 (presented by Lotringer)(Side Two, Part 2), cuid7132; 214693 (Case 221.0507)
      TRT: 01:04:56
    - Lectures by New French Critics, Sorbonne, 1964 (presented by Lotringer)(Side Three, Part 1), cuid7133; 214694 (Case 221.0509)
      TRT: 01:11:55
    - Lectures by New French Critics, Sorbonne, 1964 (presented by Lotringer)(Side Three, Part 2), cuid7134; 214695 (Case 221.0511)
      TRT: 00:23:43
    - Lectures by New French Critics, Sorbonne, 1964 (presented by Lotringer)(Side Four, Part 1), cuid7135; 214696 (Case 221.0513)
      TRT: 00:31:16
      Original Format: Audio Cassette
    - Lectures by New French Critics, Sorbonne, 1964 (presented by Lotringer)(Side Four, Part 2), cuid7136; 214697 (Case 221.0515)
      TRT: 00:30:33
    - Interview with Brendan Behan, Dublin, Jan 1961 - Reel 2 (Side 1), January 1961; cuid7137; 214698 (Case 221.0517)
      TRT: 01:03:58
    - Interview with Brendan Behan, Dublin, Jan 1961 - Reel 2 (Side 2), January 1961; ID: 221.0519; 214699 (Case 221.0519)
      TRT: 01:06:33
    - Interview with Richard Kern, April 13, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) (Part 1), ID: 221.0521; 214775 (Case 221.0521)
    - Interview with Richard Kern, April 13, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) (Part 2), ID:221.0523; 214776 (Case 221.0523)
    - Interview with Kiki Smith, June 6, 1995 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) (Side One, Part 1), ID:221.0525; 214777 (Case 221.0525)
      TRT: 00:48:01
    - Interview with Kiki Smith, June 6, 1995 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) (Side One, Part 2), ID:221.0527; 214778 (Case 221.0527)
      TRT: 00:33:36
    - Interview with Kiki Smith, April 28, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) - tape 1 (Side One, Part 1), June 6, 1995; ID:221.0529; 214779 (Case 221.0529)
      TRT: 00:31:42
    - Interview with Kiki Smith, April 28, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) - tape 1 (Side One, Part 2), ID:221.0531; 214780 (Case 221.0531)
      TRT: 00:31:44
    - Interview with Kiki Smith, April 28, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) - tape 2, ID:221.0533; 214781 (Case 221.0533)
      TRT: 00:06:35
    - Interview with Tommy Turner, March 23, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) (Side One, Part 1), ID:221.0535; 214782 (Case 221.0535)
      TRT: 00:32:10
    - Interview with Tommy Turner, March 23, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) (Side One, Part 2), ID:221.0537; 214783 (Case 221.0537)
      TRT: 00:32:09
    - Interview with Steve Doughton, April 20, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz), ID:221.0539; 214784 (Case 221.0539)
      TRT: 00:31:41
    - Interview with Steve Doughton, April 20, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz), ID:221.0541; 214785 (Case 221.0541)
      TRT: 00:29:26
    - Interview with Julie Hair, April 27, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) - tape 1 (Side One, Part 1), ID:221.0543; 214786 (Case 221.0543)
      TRT: 00:31:47
    - Interview with Julie Hair, April 27, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) - tape 1 (Side One, Part 2), ID:221.0545; 214787 (Case 221.0545)
      TRT: 00:31:28
    - Interview with Julie Hair, April 27, 1994 (for S.L.'s book on Wojnarowicz) - tape 2, ID:221.0547; 214788 (Case 221.0547)
      TRT: 00:52:10
    - S.L. Film "How to Shoot a Crime": Music from the Shining, undated; ID:221.0245; 278982 (Case 221.0245_pt.1, Case 221.0245_pt.2)
      Material is on two CDs. Please request Part 1 and Part 2.
    - Kathy Acker and Whitney Conference on Nancy Holt and Lightning Over Water, 1984-11; cuid7158 (E-records fales_mss221, E-records cuid7158)
      Format: Broadcast WAV
      TRT: 00:63:00
    - Kathy Acker/Sylvère Interview, 1989-10-10; cuid7160 (E-records fales_mss221, E-records cuid7160)
      TRT: 00:64:00
    - Kathy Acker (New York), 1989-10-10; cuid7161 (E-records fales_mss221, E-records cuid7161)
      TRT: 01:47:00
    - Kathy Acker, 1990-04-24; cuid7162 (E-records fales_mss221, E-records cuid7162)
      TRT: 01:04:00
    - Kathy Acker (3), 1990-04-24; cuid7165 (E-records fales_mss221, E-records cuid7165)
    - David Rattray, 1992; cuid7166 (E-records fales_mss221, E-records cuid7166)
      TRT: 01:26:00
  - Subseries B: Originals - Audio, 155696
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 1 (William Burroughs, excepts from Naked Lunch), 1975; ID 221.0191; 155904 (Box 83, Media ID 221.0191)
      Format: 1/4 in. reel to reel
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 2, 1975; ID 221.0192; 155905 (Box 83, Media ID 221.0192)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 3 (William Burroughs, Allen Ginsberg: Yage Letters, part 2 of 2), 1975; ID 221.0193; 155906 (Box 83, Media ID 221.0193)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 4 (William Burroughs, The Last Words of Dutch Schultz), 1975; ID 221.0194; 155907 (Box 83, Media ID 221.0194)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 5 (William Burroughs, The Last Words of Dutch Schultz), 1975; ID 221.0195; 155908 (Box 83, Media ID 221.0195)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 6 (William Burroughs, Naked Lunch, part 1 of 2), 1975; ID 221.0196; 155909 (Box 83, Media ID 221.0196)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 7 (William Burroughs, Allen Ginsburg: Yage Letters, part 1 of 2), 1975; ID 221.0197; 155910 (Box 83, Media ID 221.0197)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 8 (William Burroughs, Naked Lunch, part 2 of 2), 1975; ID 221.0198; 155911 (Box 83, Media ID 221.0198)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 9 (Intro: Lotringer/ Rajchman), 1975; ID 221.0199; 156065 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0199)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 10 (Fassender), 1975; ID 221.0200; 156066 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0200)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 11 (Fine on Panopticon), 1975; ID 221.0201; 156067 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0201)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 12 (Fine cont/ responses), 1975; ID 221.0202; 156068 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0202)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 13 (Danto? Kovel?), 1975; ID 221.0203; 156069 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0203)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 14 (Danto, Lyotard), 1975; ID 221.0204; 156070 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0204)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 15 (Lyotard), 1975; ID 221.0205; 156071 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0205)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 16 (Lyotard), 1975; ID 221.0206; 156072 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0206)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 17 (Lyotard), 1975; ID 221.0207; 156073 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0207)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 18, 1975; ID 221.0208; 156074 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0208)
    - Schizo-Culture Conference audio - reel 19, 1975; ID 221.0209; 156075 (Box 84, Media ID 221.0209)
    - Jean-Paul Sartre lecture: "Theatre dramatique et theatre epique", Sorbonne, late 50s; ID 221.0210; 156076 (Box 85, Media ID 221.0210)